onlinedataentryjob.com 2018-03-10

# Online Data Entry Job | Online Jobs | Earn Money Online | Work from home

* onlinedataentryjob.com as a socially responsible website respects user privacy and the company vouches that it will do everything within its limits to safeguard user privacy. The below privacy policy may be revised as and when seen appropriate by the company without prior notice. The below privacy policy tells how and what information is gathered from the users and how the information gathered will be used by the Company. Kindly read carefully our privacy policy hereunder and by using this website you express your acceptance of the below privacy policy. In case you have any objections or in case you do not accept our privacy policy, kindly restrain yourself from using the services of our website.

* onlinedataentryjob.com in order to provide its users with complete range of its services collects certain information from the users. The information collected includes but not limited to contact information including, phone number, email address, postal address and other personal information such as data of birth, first name, surname, etc., required to verify the identity of the users.

* The personal data collected will be used only for internal purposes and the personal data will not be shared with any third parties or the personal data will not be sold to any third parties. Information such as contact information and postal address may be shared with service partners so as to fulfill the service as in the case of product shipping and delivery.

* The personal data collected in this website may be used to understand the website demographics and the data may be used to devise future marketing plans.

* onlinedataentryjob.com does not send spam mails to the users. However, service related communications and newsletters may be sent to the registered users from time to time to keep the users up to date with the website's services.

* onlinedataentryjob.com uses cookies to collect user information such as the IP address of the users, location of the user based on the IP, date and time of visit and other data such as the browser type, etc., which may not be used to lead to individual's identity in any way. We use the information collected here to improve upon our own services by understanding the nature of our website visitors so that we can serve you better. Though you are free to switch off your browser cookies such an action may prevent you from accessing certain features of our services and our website. You may also face problems in logging into your user account when the browser cookies are switched off.

* You are free to update your account information anytime you like, though certain aspects of your account information such as your username may not be changed as this information is used to identify your account.

* onlinedataentryjob.com has taken all the required security measures to provide you with a secure online platform. You are however required to keep your computer protected from viruses and other malware programs to prevent data loss and security issues. onlinedataentryjob.com does not use or promote any malware programs.

* All the financial information including credit card, debit card information will be held confidential and no third parties will have access to such information.

* In case of the termination of the accounts you should contact the support team with your account termination request. Your request will be processed promptly and your account will be terminated within a reasonable time period. 

* onlinedataentryjob.com will not reveal the contact details and earnings of an user to other users or visitors on the site.

* If there is any Technical Problem, until we solve it you have to co-operate with us.

*You may use graphic and text links both on your website and in emails. The site may also be advertised "offline" in classified ads, magazines, and newpapers. You may use the graphics and text provided to you by us, or you may create your own as long as they are deemed appropriate according to the conditions.

* onlinedataentryjob.com does not share any data collected from the users with the other users of the website what so ever. Also onlinedataentryjob.com does not send any emails or make phone calls asking for any other personal information. You are required to report such mails or communications to onlinedataentryjob.com to protect your own interests.

* onlinedataentryjob.com and its services are not meant for minors. By making use of this website you guarantee that you are aged 18+. Our website does not collect or store information of minors.

In case of any questions or doubts regarding to our privacy policy, feel free to contact us anytime. You are encouraged to visit this page regularly and keep yourself up to date with our latest privacy policy.
